A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, John D. Rockefeller, Sr., Series A FA310
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence - Pack - Patteson (Box 20, Folder 151)
  Pack, Charles L. (Mrs.), 1928 - 1930. Lakewood visiting nurse association, book.Paddleford, G. M., January 24, 1922. Friendly greetings.Paddock, Royce, March 23, 1924. Condolence.Padiorna, Pedro, June 12, 1929. Sends plates from Mexico.Paine, Silas, April 1921. Condolence.Palmer, Edith S., (Leslie R., Mrs.), July 1922. Visit.Palmer, William P., (Mr. and Mrs.), June 1927. Wedding invitation.Pannill, Fitzhugh C., July - August 1929. Dime.Parish, Lillian T., October 4, 1930. Sent poem.Park Avenue Baptist Church, 1925 - 1929. John D. Rockefeller's contributions.Parker, Georgia, June 8, 1929. Teagle relation, visit.Parker, Joseph T., 1920 - 1922; 1929. Lakewood employee.Parker, M. B., June 1921. Visit grounds.Parker, Martha M., March 5, 1931. Autograph.Parker, Oliver J., March 10, 1930. Golf.Parker Brothers, July 21, 1930. New game "Camelot" as good as "Numerica".Parkhurst, John J., (Mr. and Mrs.), July 16, 1931. Thank you for Anniversary greetings.Parment, Reginia, and Auguste de, January 20, 1926. Tutor nurse for boys. Dimes.Parnell, Edward, (Mr. and Mrs.), June 9, 1925. Gift.Parnell, Harry, (Mr. and Mrs.), August 1928. Marriage announcement.Parrish, James C., July - August 1921. Golf.Parsons, Ellen, (Mrs.), 1926; 1930 - 1931. Cousin of Laurance S. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller gifts.Parsons, Georgiana H., (Mrs.), 1922. Birthday wishes, unhappy over Standard Oil.Parsons, H. A., (Mr. and Mrs.), November 1921. Appreciation for sympathy.Parsons, Mabel, September 1926. Personal appeal.Partridge, Frank, July 11, 1930. Birthday wishes.Paskins, Louise N., (Mrs.), March - April 1927. Old days in Cleveland.Patterson, E. B., March 5, 1924. Church appeal.Patteson, Robert A., 1920 - 1931. President, Tarrytown bank. Please use new money in cashing checks. Golf. Gifts.
- Correspondence - Paul Kimball Hospital, 1919-1930 (Box 20, Folder 152)
  John D. Rockefeller gifts.
- Correspondence - Payne, C. N. (Mrs.) - Pinnera (Box 20, Folder 153)
  Payne, Calvin N., (Mrs.), September 1926. Condolence.Payne, Dora, 1925 - 1931. Kykuit housekeeper, Christmas greetings.Payne, Homer B., August 1924. Death of father, a Standard Oil employee.Peabody, Henry W., 1921; 1925. Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) buildings, thanks to John D. Rockefeller.Peabody, S. J., 1926 - 1930. Activities in Daytona Beach.Peacock, Emily F., 1920 - 1921. Sends John D. Rockefeller a cockerel.Pearson, F. J., August - October 1927. John D. Rockefeller send photo to China post of United States Infantry.Pease, Robert A., March 24, 1927. Sends poem, "Ledger A".Peet, Lucy, (Mrs. Edward), September 1927. Church appeal.Peirce, C. H., July 9, 1921. Birthday wishes.Pence, W. E., June 3, 1930. Dime.Penfield, Georgia M., August 1921. Personal loan.Pennington, Mabel, 1921. Gift.Penrose, Stephen B. L., 1928; 1929. Tribute to John D. Rockefeller.Perkins, Evelyn, (Mrs. George W.), June - September 1920. Condolence.Perkins, Norman H., June 25, 1931. Golf.Perry, Amy, (Mrs.), 1921; 1926. Pocantico appeals.Peterjohn, Edward, October 10, 1929. Church appeal.Peters, Isaphene, 1922 - 1924. Chautauqua appeal.Peterson, F., (Mrs.), 1927. Church appeal.Peterson, Mary, (Mrs.), 1930 - 1931. Box bushes for sale.Pett, A. W., December 24, 1928. Mrs. Willard sends her best.Pettit, R. E., October 1926. John D. Rockefeller did not visit Santa Clara Valley with J. P. Morgan.Pettus, Martha E., April 28, 1931. Personal appeal.Phares, Mary, March 1930. Request interview.Phelps, Jessie C., April 4, 1930. Sends poem.Phelps, William W., August 17, 1920. Birthday wishes.Phillips, Jean O., December 11, 1927. Condolence.Phillips, M. A., December 1929. Job applicant.Phillips, Martha C., September 1922. Visit.Phillips, Reginald G. A., (Mr. & Mrs.), September 1929. Wedding announcement.Phoenix Chamber of Commerce, 1926 - 1927. John D. Rockefeller made a member of Chambers Hall of Fame.Piazzi, Ida C., (Mrs.), September 1926. Personal loan.Pierce, Louise H., (Mrs. George D.), 1928 - 1931. Sends book.Pierson, A. W., August - October 1931. Grave of Samuel Avery.Pierson, Georgiana B., (Mrs.), June 21, 1924. Personal appeal.Pilgrim Memorial Fund, September 1919. Denominational appeal.Pinnera, Gina, 1931. Sang for John D. Rockefeller in his home.
- Correspondence - Piper - Poth (Box 20, Folder 154)
  Piper, George S., December 20, 1921. Visit.Platt, Beatrice, 1930. Greetings.Platt, Caroline L., February 1924. Visit with John D. Rockefeller, Jr.Platt, Margaret, 1919. Visit.Platz, Samuel, (Mrs.), January 4, 1925. Met John D. Rockefeller in church.Pocantico Hills Lyceum, 1922; 1926 - 1931. John D. Rockefeller contributions.Pocantico Hills Union Church, 1927 - 1931. John D. Rockefeller contributions.Pocono Manor, 1920. John D. Rockefeller tries Manor spring water.Poe, Merle N., September 1930. Sends Princeton class address.Pogson, Bessie M., January 6, 1932. Christmas gifts.Pogson, Charles (brother of Bessie Pogson), 1928 - 1929. Wedding gift.Pollard, Arthur G., 1920 - 1930. Birthday greetings.Pollack, Robert E., March - April 1931. Job applicant.Pomeroy, (Miss), November 27, 1924. Thanks.Ponce Baptist Church, Puerto Rico, February 28, 1931. John D. Rockefeller made honorary member.Pool, Helen E., February 18, 1927. Library appeal.Porter, Alexander J. (Mr. and Mrs.), October 1926. Wedding invitation.Portland Advertising Club, November - December 1930. John D. Rockefeller dime auctioned for $50.Post, Jacob, August 1925. Wedding invitation.Poth, Harry A., Jr., March 13, 1928. Dime.
- Correspondence - Potter - Price, H. (Box 21, Folder 155)
  Potter, D. C., July 1926. Sends book of verse.Pouch, Susan D., (Mrs. A. B.), November 1, 1927. Personal appeal.Powel, Elizabeth B., (Mrs.), 1929. Church appeal.Powell, Eula, August 10, 1930. Sends picture.Powell, Francis E., 1924 - 1928. Recalls Henry Ford's comment on why Standard Oil was great, visit.Powell, John, (Mrs.), May 1931. Personal appeal.Powles, Mary L., September - October 1924. Personal appeal.Prairie Oil and Gas Company, April 1921. Sorry John D. Rockefeller is no longer a stockholder.Pratt, Florence G., June 1927. Wedding gift.Pratt, Hariett, June 1923. Wedding gift.Pratt, John T., (Mrs.), 1927; 1928. Condolence. Wedding invitation.Pratt, John T., Jr., August 1926. Wedding invitation.Pratt, Pauline, (no date), Wedding gift.Pratt, Ruth, 1927. Thanks for sympathy.Pratt, Virginia 1926. Wedding gift.Preble, Ida W., (Mrs.), 1923 - 1924. Bishop Lawrence's references to John D. Rockefeller.Preiss, Anna, (Mrs.), 1928. Birthday wishes, personal appeal.Prentice, John Hill, (Mr. and Mrs.), (no date), Wedding invitations, gift.Prentice, Robert K., (Mr. and Mrs.), May 1926. Wedding invitation.Prentice, Sartell, 1919 - 1922; 1925 - 1931. Christmas gifts, Ezra Parmelee relation.Prentiss, Elizabeth, (Mrs. F. F.), 1918 - 1919, 1924; 1931. Visits, gifts, golf.Prentiss, Gertrude, November 11, 1922. Personal appeal.Preuster, A. B., February 1923. Best wishes.Price, Hubert, (Mr. and Mrs.), 1924 - 1930. Florida friends, Investment advice.
- Correspondence - Price, J. H. - Puzo (Box 21, Folder 156)
  Price, J. H., 1930. Sends poems.Price, Mary B., (Mrs. J. D.), 1923 - 1925. Rockefeller Institute recommendation requested.Price, Theodore H., (Mr. and Mrs.), October 1931. Wedding invitation.Prizer, John, August 1929. Condolence.Prudden, Lillian E., April 26, 1924. Flowers in memory of brother.Public Education Association, June 1920. John D. Rockefeller gift.Public School #30, Manhattan, May 14, 1930. John D. Rockefeller sends picture.Pugh, Helen E., 1929 - 1930. Thanks for roses. Wedding invitation.Pullen, Richard T., (Mr. and Mrs.), September 1922. Marriage announcement.Puzo, Antonio, July 24, 1931. Sends poem.
- Correspondence - (Q) (Box 21, Folder 157)
  Quay, Lottie M., (Mrs.), July 12 1921. Personal appeal.Quayle, George L., March 1923. Remembers early Cleveland.Quigley, Gertrude B., September 28, 1923. Appeal for upstate relation.Quilling, N. A., 1920 - 1929. Forest Hill Park, gifts, retainer fees.Quinn, James, 1919 - 1928. Old employee, personal appeal, gift.Quisby, W. H., (Mrs.), December 31, 1929. Christmas wishes.
- Correspondence - Radcliffe - Reliance Hose Company #4 (Box 21, Folder 158)
  Radcliffe, W. K., 1920 - 1922; 1927 - 1928. Sunday School pupil, visit, condolence.Raineri, Jessie W., (Mrs. R.), November 8, 1926. Personal appeal.Ralph, William, August 1921. John D. Rockefeller pays hospital bill.Ramsay, Georgina M., 1925 - 1926; 1929; 1931. Visits to gardens.Randall, Katherine P., (Mrs. Paul K.), December 14, 1928. Dime.Randolph, Teasdale, July 1923. Personal appeal.Rankin, Mildred, March 21, 1931. Sends picture of John D. Rockefeller.Rapport-Hoffman Dress Corporation, October - November 1929. Thanks for stock market statement.Rasely, George, January 8, 1928. Thanks for gift.Rathbun, Annie A., April 25, 1929. Servant girl, poem.Ratliff, T. A., November 5, 1928. Tribute to Noguchi.Rauschenbusch, Pauline, (Mrs. Walter), 1920 - 1931. Children's activities, personal struggles, memories of Walter, gifts.Raymond Pynchon & Company, 1926. Arrangements with brokerage house.Red Cross, Christmas Seal Fund, December 8, 1929. John D. Rockefeller gift.Redfearn, Paul L., February 1929. Church appeal.Reed, Anna, (Mrs.), January 16, 1930. Personal appeal.Redd, H. O., July 18, 1919 - 1931. Spelman cousin.Rees, Thomas, (Mr. and Mrs.), 1927; 1930. Sends book.Reese, Charles N., April 25, 1921. Got nickel in March, has had to sell.Reeves, William C., January 20, 1930. Thanks for gift, Baptist Annuity Board.Reily, E. J., February 14, 1931. Asks for visit.Reilly, M., (Mrs.), February 1, 1926. Personal appeal.Reilly, Myrta G., (Mrs. John A.), March 1931. Condolence.Reliance Hose Company #4, November - December 1919. John D. Rockefeller donations to Lakewood company.
- Correspondence - Renato - Richmond, J. M. (Box 21, Folder 159)
  Renato, Masillo, March - April 1927. Sends John D. Rockefeller photograph.Republican National Committee, 1920; 1926 - 1930. John D. Rockefeller contributions.Reuschline, George L., October 1930. Gift for work done at Pocantico Hills.Reynolds, Henry L., January 8, 1930. Job application.Reynolds, L. R., 1923 - 1924. John D. Rockefeller gifts to Halifax Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA).Reynolds, Thomas, January 21, 1922. Thanks for check.Reynolds, William J., 1927. Condolences.Rhodes, Ellis B., 1924 - 1931. Sends 1908 pictures of John D. Rockefeller.Richards, Sallie D., October 6, 1930. Sends poem.Richards, Warren G., 1922; 1928. Memories of Forest Hill.Richardson, Edythe, (Mrs. B. F.), May 1931. Appeal.Richardson, W. T. R., April 19, 1927. Personal appeal, Farmer messenger, for Standard Oil.Richardson, Willard S., 1926 - 1931. Gifts to family; enclosing letter of 1879.Richdale, Frank L., April 19, 1930. Visit.Richmond, H. W., (Mrs.), July 30, 1927. Appeal.Richmond, Dr. John M., 1920 - 1931. Ormond Union Church minister, John D. Rockefeller gifts, visits to Casements.
- Correspondence - Riedemann - Rockefeller, Alice M. (Box 21, Folder 160)
  Riedemann, H., 1922; 1926 - 1927. Visit of German Oilman.Rigby, George L., September 1924. Marriage announcement.Rigby, George N., 1921 - 1930. Mayor of Ormond, friendship, assistance to son.Ritchie, Beatrice, June 1928. Wedding gift.Riverside Church, 1929 - 1930. Opening calendar, John D. Rockefeller gift.Robbins, Julia S., 1920 - 1921. Gifts.Roberts, Beulah, (Mrs.), January 1923. Niece, visit, dimes.Roberts, Edward A., 1921; 1931. Beulah Roberts husband, visits, business opportunities.Roberts, Isabel H., (Mrs.), May 1920. Gift for dependent children.Robertson, Frieda W., May 23, 1930. Hospital appeal.Robertson, John W., 1921 - 1922. Visits.Robinson, Ida S., (Mrs.), 1920 - 1921. Second cousin, gifts, visits.Roche, Patrick, 1921 - 1922. Farmer employee, backstairs gossip.Rockafellow, Benjamin F., 1919 - 1920; 1926. Canon City, Colorado, Rockefeller Family Association, condolence.Rockefeller, Alice M., 1920; 1926; 1930 - 1931. Frank Rockefeller's daughter, gifts.
- Correspondence - Rockefeller, Allen C. - Rockefeller, Charles (Mrs.) (Box 21, Folder 161)
  Rockefeller, Allen C., 1922 - 1931. Dryden, New York. John D. Rockefeller gifts, Injury to foot.Rockefeller, Anna E., September 23, 1930. Wisconsin, personal appeal.Rockefeller, Arthur W., October 19, 1931. Personal appeal.Rockefeller, Asahel, 1926 - 1931. Phelps, New York. John D. Rockefeller gifts to son of cousin.Rockefeller, Avery, September 1923. Marriage announcement.Rockefeller, Bertha C., July 6, 1931. Lebanon, New Jersey, Birthday greeting.Rockefeller, Carrie, 1921 - 1925. Clifton Springs, New Jersey, daughter of Asahel B. Rockefeller, birthday wishes.Rockefeller, Charles, (Mrs.), 1920; 1928 - 1931. Rochester, New York. Comments on character, gifts.
- Correspondence - Rockefeller, Eleanor - Rockefeller, Jacob (Box 22, Folder 162)
  Rockefeller, Eleanor, 1919 - 1921. Brooklyn, New York. Medical help.Rockefeller, Ella, December 20, 1930. Rochester, New York. Gift.Rockefeller, Egbert and Georgia, 1919 - 1930. New London, Ohio, gifts.Rockefeller, Faith, August 16, 1930. Greenwich, Connecticut. Visit.Rockefeller, F. S., August 1929. Pitman, New Jersey. Visited New York.Rockefeller, Godfrey S., 1923; 1930. Greenwich, Connecticut. Orange grove, wedding gift.Rockefeller, Henry, (Mrs.), 1920. Dryden, Ohio, gifts.Rockefeller, Henry O., 1921 - 1922; 1928 - 1931. Brooklyn, New York, Family Association.Rockefeller, Jacob G., 1920 - 1931. Atlantic City, New Jersey. Gifts, birthday wishes, condolences.
- Correspondence - Rockefeller, John R. - Rockefeller, Raymond (Box 22, Folder 163)
  Rockefeller, John Robert, September 18, 1923. Flint, Michigan, personal appeal.Rockefeller, John S., 1920 - 1931. New London, Ohio, John D. Rockefeller gifts.Rockefeller, Mary, March 20, 1927. Lincoln, Illinois. Claims to be cousin.Rockefeller, Mary L., (Mrs.), 1929 - 1930. Atlantic City (Mrs. John G.), John D. Rockefeller gifts.Rockefeller, Percy A., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1925; 1928. Weddings of daughters in Greenwich, Connecticut.Rockefeller, Raymond, 1923 - 1924. Dryden, New York, Allen C. Rockefeller's son, John D. Rockefeller gifts.
- Correspondence - Rockefeller, Rossman - Rockefeller Family Association (Box 22, Folder 164)
  Rockefeller, Rossman, 1921 - 1927. Syracuse, New York. Sends Rockefeller song, sang at Hartford, family news, wife's appeal for W. Holyoke.Rockefeller, Willard O., 1929 - 1930. West Park-on-Hudson, New York. John D. Rockefeller gift.Rockefeller, William A., June 1931. Marriage announcement.Rockefeller Family Association, 1923 - 1926. Announcements, John D. Rockefeller dues.
- Correspondence - Rockwell - Round (Box 22, Folder 165)
  Rockwell, Camden O., May 1922. Relative of Garfield, Tribute to John D. Rockefeller.Rodeheaver, Homer, 1928 - 1930. Golf, songs sung for Mr. Rockefeller.Roe, Livingston, April 1925. Condolence.Roe, Margaret E., 1921 - 1931. Brooktondale, New York, relative, John D. Rockefeller gift.Rodgers, Eric W., January - February 1929. Editorial Greensboro, North Carolina.Rogers, Henry M., July 1929. "New light" in India.Rogers, James H., 1921 - 1923; 1931. Visits.Rogers, Kate E., (Mrs.), August - September 1927. Personal appeal.Rollins College, February - March 1931. John D. Rockefeller gives stone from fountain for Walk of Fame at college.Romer, Charles, November 4, 1923. American Automobile Association.Ronalds, Charles C., March 1929. Dimes, visits.Roosa, Arthur, 1924 - 1925. Condolences.Roper, A. Kent, July 31, 1931. News of Tioga county man.Rorer, Henry S., February 1927. John D. Rockefeller sends autograph to school, (Norfolk, Virginia).Rosander, Anna, 1922; 1928. Christmas cards.Rose, Lenox S., 1923 - 1931. Wishes, flowers.Rose, W. R., 1929 - 1930. Cleveland contractor, described Rockefeller property.Rose, William G., 1923 - 1929. Memories of Cleveland, sends picture of Lincoln. John D. Rockefeller comments on 1926 "Saturday Evening Post" article.Rosenwald, Julius, June 1929. Condolences.Ross, A. C., June - July 1923. John D. Rockefeller visit to boyhood home.Ross, David R., May 1929. Dime.Round, Louis D., 1926; 1929. Visits. Invested in Standard Oil.
- Correspondence - Rowe, F. - Ryerson (Box 22, Folder 166)
  Rowe, Florence, May 1925. Wedding gift.Rowe, William V., 1922; 1929. Legal ethics. Defended Standard Oil Trust. Comments on new lawyers, request.Rowland, Davidge H., 1922. Visit.Roxton, Laura C., (Mrs.), December 1930. Invitation.Royal, Edith, (Mrs.), 1925; 1930. Memories of Euclid Avenue Baptist Church.Rudd, Frank H., 1919 - 1931. Gifts to Frank and for others through him, family news, (nephew of John D. Rockefeller).Rudd, George A., 1919 - 1930. News of store, greetings.Rule, William March 11, 1925. Editorial on John D. Rockefeller's golf.Russell, Howard H., 1920 - 1931. Anti-Saloon League work, described John D. Rockefeller attendance at temperance meeting.Russell, James E., October 25, 1923. Welfare work in Tioga county.Russell, Virginia, August 1928. Dime.Ryerson, Caroline, 1921; 1927 - 1929. Birthday, wishes, visit.
- Correspondence - Sadofsky - Sanchez (Box 22, Folder 167)
  Sadofsky, Rose, April 1924. Wedding gift.Sage, E. C., October 6, 1927. Condolence.St. John's Missionary Baptist Church, Ormond, 1922 - 1925. John D. Rockefeller contributions to colored church.Saint Joseph's Normal Institute, Pocantico Hills, October 15, 1920. John D. Rockefeller donation.Saint Joseph's Orphanage, Cleveland, April 1929. John D. Rockefeller sends cards of verse.Saint Mark's Episcopal Church, 1929 - 1930. Tarrytown. John D. Rockefeller contributions.Saint Philomena's Church, Cleveland, 1926 - 1927. Church appeals.Salvation Army, 1921; 1924; 1928 - 1931. John D. Rockefeller gifts, Evangeline Booth visit to Pocantico Hills.Sambrook, Hattie, 1920 - 1924; 1930. Companion to Miss Lucy Spelman.Sambrook, Sarah, 1919 - 1925; 1929 - 1931. John D. Rockefeller purchased family home in Cleveland, allowed Miss Sambrook to live rent free in house.Sampson, William, May 1926. 1879 letter written by John D. Rockefeller in answer to news of death in family.Sanchez, R. M., December 21, 1931. Best wishes, Mr. Manuel S. Renteria was John D. Rockefeller's New York coachman.
- Correspondence - Sanders - Seabloom (Box 22, Folder 168)
  Sanders, Henry M., July - August 1921. Condolence and will.Sanderson, Percy, March 1, 1926. Sends samples of mineral water for John D. Rockefeller from Belgium.Sandmeyer, Florence T., (Mrs. William E.), April 24, 1928. Cousin, sends picture of Forest Hill.Sangree, H., March 24, 1924. Visit.Sargent, Kathrine A., 1925; 1931. Visits.Sarvis, William H., 1924 - 1926. Remembers Cleveland school days, condolence.Saunders, Fannie E., (Mrs. C. C.), 1921; 1929. Personal appeal.Saunders, George P., November 1922. Personal appeal.Savidge, Frank R., 1920 - 1928. Visits, comments on oil industry, sends bronze likeness of John D. Rockefeller, condolence.Sawamura, S., 1930 - 1931. Friendship.Sawyer, I. H., February 1926. Visits Ormond.Sawyer, Mozelle, June 12, 1927. Best wishes.Sayford, Irving S., July 1922. Request for statement.Scales, Florence M., 1927. Visit; memory cards.Schaumann, Ethel, January 28, 1929. Sends picture of Roman antique.Schavolite Golf Corporation, 1928 - 1929. Golf clubs.Schellinger, Adolph, July 1921. Thanks for institute gardens.Schermerhorn, Marion, (Mrs.), February 20, 1929. Avery relative.Schiff, Jacob H., (Mrs.), September 1920. Condolences.Schmidt, John G., (Mrs.), November 1926. Wedding invitation.Schmidt, Raymond, September - October 1929. Educational appeal.Schneider, May, (Mrs. Daniel), March 11, 1930. Visit.Schnitzer, William M., March - April 1930. Autograph.Scholl, William, 1928 - 1931. John D. Rockefeller gifts.Schoonmaker, Nellie T., (Mrs. N. R.), July 7, 1921. Visit.Schuyler, Thelma, June 2, 1930. Thanks for milk.Sciranka, John C., May 1929. Item in Slovak press.Scofield, William M., April 12, 1919. Best wishes.Scott, Albert L., March 24, 1930. Visit.Scrimgeour, Charles E., (Mrs.), August 1921. Has patented a foot rest.Seabloom, Helena L., (Mrs. Davido), March 27, 1930. Thanks for gift.
- Correspondence - Seaman - Seubert (Box 23, Folder 169)
  Seaman, Gussie, 1919 - 1931. Golf, visits, gifts.Seattle Public Library, July - August 1931. Autograph.See, Elizabeth P., 1931. Thanks for picture.Seep, Joseph, 1925 - 1928. Best wishes, condolences.Selick, Elsie, 1930. Golf.Selick, Gladys, 1926. Wedding Gift.Sellen, Claude, (Mrs.), September 1926 - 1927. John D. Rockefeller visit to Moravia, New York.Selover, George, 1927 - 1930. Personal appeal, worked with P.D. Briggs in 1870.Sencabaugh, John T., 1929 - 1930. Old Standard Oil employee, dimes.Sethmann, W. J., November 13, 1930. Sends stock certificate.Settle, John A., January 1924. Sends new style golf tee.Seubert, Edward G., October - November 1929. Tribute to John D. Rockefeller on business condition.
- Correspondence - Sewall - Sharpe (Box 23, Folder 170)
  Sewall, Charles G., 1919 - 1930. Relative of Charles Strong, Kate Strong, family friendship, gifts, family news.Sewell, Marshall, 1924 - 1931. Minister, Lakewood Baptist Church. John D. Rockefeller gifts.Shade Tree Commission of New Jersey, 1929 - 1930. Visit to Lakewood.Shafer, I. H., (Mrs. Paul), October 13, 1928. Best wishes.Shannon, Patrick, August - September 1929. John D. Rockefeller sends picture.Sharpe, D. R., 1927 - 1929. Cleveland Baptist Association, report on work. Golf.
- Correspondence - Shatford - Shiloh Baptist Church, Tarrytown (Box 23, Folder 171)
  Shatford, S. S., March 22, 1929. Visit.Shatton, Lottie, 1930. Gift.Shaver, Lucy, (Mrs.), 1920 - 1931. Harford Mills relative, gifts.Shaw, A. W., January 1928. Tribute from Florida Boy Scouts.Shaw, Albert, 1919; 1929 - 1931. Thanks for gift to education, served on General Education Board.Shaw, William E., 1929 - 1930. Claims to be relative.Sheen, Margaret J., February 12, 1926. Tribute to Cleveland teacher.Sheldon, A. B., April 7, 1931. Sends poem.Shenandoah Post VFW, June 1926. John D. Rockefeller gift.Shepard, Helen Gould, (Mr. and Mrs. Finley, Jr.), Visits, her bible memorizing scheme.Shepherd, Herbert, September 12, 1929. Offers art for sale.Sheppard, William T., 1920 - 1931. Seabrook Farms in New Jersey. Mr. Murphy's death. Missionary problems. Visits.Sherman, C. M., 1928. Church appeal.Sherman, Ida M., August 26, 1930. Dime.Shiloh Baptist Church, Cleveland, April 9, 1929. Appeal.Shiloh Baptist Church, Tarrytown, 1919 - 1923. John D. Rockefeller donations.
- Correspondence - Shinn, G. C. - Simpson (Box 23, Folder 172)
  Shinn, Grace, 1921 - 1925. Lakewood osteopath, gifts.Shinn, Harry C., November 24, 1923. Job applicant.Shiras, George, 3rd, (Mr. and Mrs.), August 1924. Condolence.Shiras, Olive, (Mrs.), March 20, 1931. Birthday celebration.Short, Robert H., February 3, 1930. Dime.Shoup, W. W., December 10, 1926. Church appeal.Shove, Katharine, September 1919. Wedding gift.Sibley, Joseph C., 1922 - 1926. Sends box of bran flakes, tributes to John D. Rockefeller, condolence.Siegfried, Jules, October 4, 1924. Visit.Silverman, Samuel, August 28,1928. Personal appeal.Silverton, New Jersey Church, May 4, 1926. John D. Rockefeller gift.Simanton, Juliana, January 14, 1930. Gift.Sime, Edith M., Dime.Simmons University, July 8, 1927. Appeal.Simpson, Harry, (Mr. and Mrs.), August 1930. Wedding invitation.
- Correspondence - Sims, Harry D., 1919-1927 (Box 23, Folder 173)
  Chandler & Rudd. Family news Alta House. Destruction of oil company records. Needy families. Golf. Death of friends.
- Correspondence - Sims, Harry D., 1928-1931 (Box 23, Folder 174)
- Correspondence - Sinclair, I. - Smith, H. (Box 23, Folder 175)